57 Bordeaux, Block F Flat NRU 3, Triq Katerina Vitale, Xemxija San Pawl IL-Bahar, SPB 4260, Malta

+356 7934 2920 | robvibart@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-vibart-78418071



OVERVIEW

Robert is a multi-skilled Graphics designer with twelve years' experience designing a wide variety of designs, he has worked with various marketing personnel to concept, research and design campaigns for promotional print Ad-hoc, corporate collateral, and packaging design. The following are but a few of the companies that he has worked alongside – First National Bank, Investec Bank & ABSABank.

SKILLS

Project Management, Operations Manager, Diagnosis(Digital output)

Adobe CC Suite - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Flash(CS6), Maya Ver 2018, Vectary 3D (Web platform) Sketch Up 2019 Web Design - Visual Studio Code - HTML5, CSS, SASS, GitHub integration, Figma, UI, Netlify.io (Static page development), Wordpress Microsoft Word, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Excel

EMPLOYMENT

Jetline Print on Demand 2009 - 2011

Production assistant and Desktop publisher

- Worked with clients to conceptualize various Graphic design requirements for print
- Setting digital print for Litho output
- Setting packing designs for digital print output
- Setting large format designs for print output
- Logo design and concept creation
- Setting print for various finishing output
 - Foiling
 - Die cutting
 - Embossing

Studio-CX Design Studio

2012-2011

Assistant Junior Graphic designer

- Assistant to senior Graphic designer.
- Assisted with design and development of layouts for financial reports for print digital output.
- Assisted team with typesetting and layout (CAPS) curriculum educational manuals for digital output.
- Redrew various images for vector output.
- Type setting redrawing statistical graphs for Barometer financial reports for the (Development Bank South Africa) DBSA.
- Created various logos for the company and its clients.

Cube Zoo Design Studio

2012- 2012(One month Internship)

Junior Graphic designer

- Assisted with design and development of web format animated banners (Adobe Flash CS6).
- Assisted with design and development of various logos for various clients.
- Designed and developed magazine layouts and typesetting both for digital output and print output.
- Assisted with coding static HTML and CSS websites using basic Github integration

.

H.O.D of Graphic and Visual Communications Dept

- Managed and ran multiple Graphic design concepts for print output.
- Oversee print production team duties and client requests.
- Managing production time frames and digital output requests.
- Maintained company job tracking system.
- Maintained company in-house Graphic design concepts and final print output.
- Assisted marketing personnel with conceptualization and campaign development.
- Managed and communicated with various print suppliers and production managers on digital job final output.
- Designed and developed eventing print collateral for First National Bank, Rand Merchant Bank and Investec Bank using corporate CI guides

EDUCATION

Tertiary Education Willowridge High

1998 - 2002(Matriculated)

2002 - 2004

Depth Animation Studios (Internship)

- Basic 3D Animation theory
- Junior Level (Maya Software)
 - o 3D Modeling
 - o 3D Lighting and Texturing
 - o 3D Computer Arts
 - Storyboard development

Boston Media house 2005 - 2007

- Graphic design (Diploma)
- Public relations
- Communication science
- Advertising
- Marketing

Boston Media house 2007 - 2009

- 3D Animation 3D Design (Diploma)
 - o Pixilation / Stop motion animation
 - o Illustration and 2D conceptualization 2D Animation
 - Storyboard and concept development

REFERENCES

Available upon request